EPISODE 2 LOCKSMITH
TWO PEOPLE AGAINST ONE
WHAT IF I MAKE THEM MAD?
THEY'RE MAKING FUN OF ME
A WASTE OF TIME
I CAN'T GET HERE UNLESS I USE THAT CROSSWALK OVER THERE
SWIFT
BLURRY
HURRY
AFTER ALL THIS TIME
THE HURDLE TO ADDRESSING HIM
I WANTED TO KNOW HIS LAST NAME
WE'RE PRETTY CLOSE
SPARKLE SPARKLE SPARKLE SPARKLE
BANG
MEITEN COMMUNITY CENTER
WELL DONE, MOM
FLUSTER
NATURAL SPARKLING LEMON WATER
REFRESHING AND DELICIOUS APPLE JUICE
SHAKE SHAKE
I FEEL BAD
COCOA, SWEET RED BEAN SOUP,
AMAZAKE CORN POTAGE
STRETCH
SHE DOESN'T GET CALLED BY HER FIRST NAME MUCH TO BEGIN WITH
SQUISH
INCOMING CALL
HE DOES THIS IF I DON'T KEEP AN EYE ON HIM
BA-DUMP, BA-DUMP
SCHOOL NURSE'S OFFICE
RELIEVED
BRISKLY
BAM
I KIND OF LIKE IT
SPACE FOR ONE PERSON
STEPPING BACK
HUFF, HUFF
FOGGY
THEY TEND TO TALK A LITTLE MORE WHEN
THEY ARE ABOUT TO SAY GOODBYE
BECAUSE I'M ONLY A HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
ONE THOUSAND YEN
SHOP MANAGER
GRADE 1 CLASS 6
THAT WAY, IT'LL ALSO BE EASIER FOR MIKI TO CONTACT US
THAT'S TRUE